let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "1. C++ uses which approach?",
    answer: "bottom -up",
    options: [
      "right -left",
      "Top-down",
      "left-right",
      "bottom -up"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "2.By which of the following can the if-else statement be replaced?",
    answer: "Conditional operator",
    options: [
      "Bitwise operator",
      "Logical operator",
      "Conditional operator",
      "Arithmetic operator"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: " 3. When can an inline function be expanded ?",
    answer: "Compile time",
    options: [
      "Runtime",
      "Compile time",
      "Never gets expanded",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
      numb: 4,
    question: "4.Using which of the following keywords can an exception be generated??",
    answer: "throw",
    options: [
      "threw",
      "throws",
      "throw",
      "catch",
    ]
  },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "5.Identify the correct range of signed char.?",
      answer: "-128 to 127",
      options: [
        "-256 to 255",
        "-128 to 127",
        "0 to 255",
        "0 to 127"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "6. How much bytes of memory does void occupy??",
    answer: "0",
    options: [
      "1",
      "0",
      "2",
      "4",
  ]
},
{
  numb: 7,
  question: "7. Choose the option below which is not a member of class?",
  answer: "Friend function",
  options: [
    "Friend function",
    "Static function",
    "Virtual function",
    "Const function",
]
},
{
  numb: 8,
  question: "8. Under which pillar of OOPS does base class and derived class relationship come?",
  answer: "Inheritance",
  options: [
    "Polymorphism",
    "Inheritance",
    "Encapsulation",
    "Abstraction"
]
},
{
  numb: 9,
  question: "9. Which of the following functions can be inherited from base class  ?",
  answer: "None",
  options: [
    "Constructor",
    "Destructor",
    "Static",
    "None"
]
},
{
  numb: 10,
  question: "10. Which of the following is the correct identifier ?",
  answer: "var_name12",
  options: [ 
    "2var_name",
    "2VAR_NAME",
    "$varname",
    "var_name12"
]
},

];